Why would I lie to you?
Apa aku bisa membohongimu?
Miss Chen is indeed pregnant.
Nona Chen memang hamil.
The meal is ready.
Makanan sudah siap.
Shall I bring it to you now?
Apakah akan diantar sekarang?
Please let me know if you need anything.
Beri tahu aku jika kau butuh sesuatu.
Why are you following me?
Kenapa kau mengikutiku?
Aren't you his adjutant?
Bukankah kau ajudannya?
To protect your safety at all times.
Melindungi keamanan Anda tanpa meninggalkan selangkah pun.
I almost forgot.
Sepertinya aku hampir lupa.
I can't just swing on a whim.
tidak boleh sembarangan bermain ayunan.
Didn't your governor say
Bukankah gubernur kalian bilang
that he could fulfill all my wishes?
bisa memuaskan aku dalam segala hal?
As long as Miss Chen orders,
Asalkan Nona Chen perintahkan,
Then go prepare a car now.
siapkan mobil sekarang.
Now that I'm pregnant with Fang Yanyun's child,
Dia mengandung anak Fang Shi-woon.
since the governor won't let me leave,
Karena Jenderal tidak mengizinkan aku pergi,
I'll give birth here at the governor's mansion.
Kediaman Panglima sudah lahir.
Let Chen Qingyan stay in the Governor's mansion.
Membiarkan Chen Qingyan tinggal di Kediaman Panglima?
Actually, I'm quite envious of you.
Sebenarnya aku sangat iri padamu.
She can still make you worry so much.
masih bisa membuatmu khawatir.
That's why they say you're capable of great things.
Atau kamu bisa melakukan hal besar.
You're being cuckolded and happily becoming a father.
Kau menjadi ayah dengan tuduhan palsu.
Now everyone in the mansion knows about it.
membuat seluruh kediaman tahu.
This bastard child staying in the Governor's mansion.
Anak haram ini tinggal di Kediaman Panglima,
Either get rid of the child,
atau bunuh anak itu.
or leave with her.
atau kau pergi bersamanya.
There's no other choice.
Tidak ada pilihan lain.
It will be like a natural miscarriage.
Akan seperti keguguran alami.
Put the pears into the pot.
memasukkan pir ke dalam panci.
Haven't you added a bit too much?
Apakah kamu menambahkan terlalu banyak?
I thought you had died in battle.
Kukira kau sudah mati.
So you're that eager for me to die?
Kau begitu berharap aku mati?
You lock me up here and then avoid me.
Kau mengurungku di sini dan menghindariku.
As long as you're willing to stay.
Selama kau mau tinggal,
Everyone in the mansion knows.
seluruh keluarga tahu
This is not your child.
ini bukan anakmu.
General, don't you even care about your own
Apakah gubernur bahkan
reputation anymore?
harga diri sendiri?
My affairs are none of their business.
Urusanku belum giliran mereka.
The general specifically instructed,
Jenderal telah berpesan,
you must have proper meals three times a day.
Anda harus makan tiga kali sehari dengan baik.
even if you can't eat,
Meski kau tidak bisa makan,
you should think of the child.
juga harus memikirkan anak.
This is made with wild ginseng from Yunshui Mountain.
Ini ginseng liar Gunung Yunshui.
I heard the general personally led people to collect it.
Dengar-dengar, Jenderal khusus membawa orang untuk mengambilnya.
I'm at their mercy.
Manusia sebagai pisau, aku adalah daging ikan.
Your blood is indeed cold.
Darahmu memang sangat dingin.
Why don't you have some snacks instead?
Bagaimana jika kau makan camilan?
As long as you're willing to stay,
Asalkan kamu bersedia tinggal,
Dr. Chen's morning sickness is so severe.
Dokter Chen mual kehamilan begitu parah?
Are you really not hungry?
Apa kau tidak berselera makan?
You should try to understand Leng Sinian.
Kau juga harus memahami Tahun Leng Si.
He's already fallen out with the Lin family for your sake.
Demi kau, dia sudah putus dengan Keluarga Lin.
Now you're pregnant with someone else's child.
Sekarang kau mengandung anak orang lain.
It's difficult to explain to the Shuai family.
Sulit untuk menjelaskan kepada Jenderal.
He doesn't want the position of military governor.
Dia tidak menginginkan posisi Jenderal.
If he intended to let you go,
Jika dia berencana melepaskanmu,
you wouldn't have drunk the soup with musk in it.
kau tak akan minum sup dengan wewangian.
The gentle breeze caresses.
Angin sepoi-sepoi mendekat
The gentle breeze softly stirs your heart.
Angin sepoi-sepoi menyentuh hatimu
The gentle breeze softly caresses.
Angin sepoi-sepoi menggoda
The lake water reflects me clearly.
Air danau menyinari aku
Falling leaves cover the ground, as if you're gently here.
Daun berguguran, seperti kamu yang ringan
The rustling of falling leaves seems like your soft whisper.
Daun berguguran, seperti mendengar kata-katamu
How many times have the flowers bloomed?
Bunga bermekaran beberapa kali.
How many times have the flowers bloomed? The rain falls silently.
Bunga bermekaran beberapa kali, hujan tidak berhenti.
Together, yet in vain.
Saling mengandalkan, sia-sia.
Looking at you, longing to be together, all in vain.
Melihatmu, saling mengandalkan, sia-sia niat.
Looking at you, shaping our togetherness, all in vain.
Memandangmu, saling mengandalkan, sia-sia niat.
Looking, if it's you, longing to be together.
Berharap, jika kamu, saling mengandalkan.
Yet unable to resist, the heart's law.
Tapi tidak menolak, hati menegakkan hukum.
Yet unable to resist, the heart's obsession.
Tapi tidak bisa menolak, terobsesi.
If persistent, if following the heart, if desired.
Jika bersikeras, jika mengikuti kata hati, seperti di mana saja.
If insistent,
Jika bersikeras,
following the heart, if desired.
Lakukan sesukamu.
If insistent, if following the heart, if desired.
Jika bersikeras bertindak sesuka hati
Delusional to occupy tender moments.
Berkhayal menguasai, menyimpan waktu
The night sways like your silhouette.
Malam bergoyang seperti bayanganmu
Walking alone under the moon, memories surge.
Kenangan muncul sendirian di bawah bulan
In dreams, returning to the past, searching for traces.
Memimpikan masa lalu, mencari jejak.
In dreams, returning to the past, searching for remaining traces.
Bermimpi kembali ke masa lalu, mencari jejak yang tersisa.
In dreams, returning to the past, finding remaining traces.
Mimpi kembali mencari jejak yang tersisa
(The Milky Way stretches for thousands of miles, love beyond the horizon.
Sungai bintang melintasi langit
The river stretches for thousands of miles, love beyond the horizon.
Sungai dan sungai, pernah mencintai langit.
Protecting you, what to believe, what is love?
Menjaga kamu, bagaimana percaya apa itu cinta?
Silently guarding, foolishly pursuing.
Diam-diam melindungi dan mengejar
I hold you, true, singing directly.
Aku memelukmu sungguh YongZhi
I have you, using a true heart to sing sincerely.
Aku memilikimu dengan ketulusan hati
Not in vain to be moved, seeking to love fully.
Tidak sia-sia tergerak dan memohon untuk puas.
Soon to be moved, seeking to love fully.
Tidak lama jatuh cinta, mohon bersenang-senang.
In vain to be moved, seeking to love fully.
Sia-sia jatuh cinta, memohon untuk bersenang-senang.